

Gabriel Danaila

WEB DEVELOPER

gabriel.danaila.tech@gmail.com www.gabrieldanaila.com Tel: +4 0733 665 934

WORK EXPERIENCE

iDesign - Netherlands
Digital Agency

Mar 2019 - Present

Web Developer - Freelancer

- I developed diverse responsive modules for Toyota and Ring, designed to enhance their website platforms. My responsibilities included developing these modules and conducting bug fixes according to client requirements, utilising technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript to accomplish these tasks.
- I worked on various projects, including server and database-integrated applications, JavaScript games, and structurally designed landing pages. I used Visual Studio Code as my main code editor.
- Utilised Bootstrap to create a unified and adaptive user interface,
 optimising cross-device compatibility and enhancing user engagement

Nissan - USA

Feb 2011 - Feb 2019

Battery Manufacturing Plant for Electric Vehicles

Engineer Technician

- As a member of the technical team, my responsibilities included the operation and programming of Mitsubishi and Yamaha industrial robots.
- I was responsible for maintaining automated equipment, using program backups, PLC diagnostic software, and perform calibration for cameras and sensors. Expertise in operating Omron Programmable Logic Controllers and managing Omron Vision System hardware and software

Leviton - USA

Feb 2007 - Feb 2011

Distribution Center Facilities

Engineer Technician

 I had the role of maintaining automated equipment over an extended period, which involved utilising a variety of backup programs and diagnostic software, as well as programming and calibrating various systems.

SKILLS

- React
- · JavaScript
- HTML
- · CSS
- Node
- MongoDB
- · Visual Studio Code

HIGHLIGHTS

With over 10 years of experience, I've applied my extensive knowledge in web development and technical engineering.

Over time, I transitioned into a full-stack developer role, and in recent years, I've pursued various courses to continuously enhance my skills and implement a range of technologies, including React, JavaScript, and HTML.

EDUCATION

Science Degree in Engineering (SIA) -Technology and Quality Control. University of Galati , 1998 – 2004

LANGUAGES

English – Fluent Romanian - Native